choyungtea.com 2015-03-30

# Cho-Yung Weight Loss Tea | Green Tea for Weight Loss • Cho-Yung

Cho-Yung (Cyprus) Limited ( **"We"; "Us"** ) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to therein), sets out the basis on which any personal data We collect from you, or that you provide to Us, will be processed by Us. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how We will treat it.

**1\. DATA CONTROLLER**

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **"Act"** ), the Data Controller is Cho-Yung (Cyprus) Limited **,** a company incorporated in registered in Cyprus under company number HE273919 having its registered office at Eressou 1, Mesa Geitonia, 4002, Limassol, Cyprus (VAT No: 10273919L).

**2\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

The information we collect from you may vary depending on whether you are logged in to our website http://www.choyungtea.com (the **"Website"** ).

We may collect and process the following data about you:

(a)          information that you provide when you use our Website. This includes information provided at the time you Register an Account and information entered by you at any time you Order through the Website. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website;

(b)          if you contact Us by telephone or in writing, We may keep a copy of that correspondence or communication;

(c)          details of transactions you carry out through the Website or any third party sites accessed via the Website, and of fulfilment of any orders you place on the Website; and

(d)          details of your visits to the Website and the resources that you access.

If you have provided Us with the personal data of another person, you confirm that he/she consents to the processing of his/her personal data and that you have informed him/her of our identity as a Data Controller and provided him/her with a copy of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

**3\. IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your mobile phone, computer or other device from which you access the Website including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for systems administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. We may, however, use such information in conjunction with the data we have about you in order to track your usage of our services.

Our Website uses cookies (small files stored by your browser that allow it to recognise you as a user and store your preferred settings). Cookies are widely used to make websites function efficiently

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website, including areas offering special offers. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log in to our Website.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which We have no control.

**4\. RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take appropriate measures to ensure that any information collected from you is kept secure and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purpose for which such information is used.

If any of your personal data changes, or if you have any questions about how We use data collected which relates to you, please contact Us using the details below.

We normally update your personal data within seven (7) working days of any new or updated personal data being provided to Us, to ensure that the personal data We hold about you is as accurate and up to date as possible.

**5\. USES MADE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

(a)          to ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device;

(b)          to provide you with information, products and/or services that you request from Us or which We feel may interest you;

(c)          to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and Us;

(d)          to contact and notify promotion winners; and

(e)          to notify you about changes to our services.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data the Order Form.

**6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

(a)          in the event that We sell or buy any business or assets, in which case We may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; or

(b)          if We or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about our customers will be one of the transferred assets; or

(c)          if We are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or

(d)          to protect the rights, property or safety of Cho-Yung (Cyprus) Limited, our customers and users or others.

**7\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask Us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if We intend to use your data for such purposes or if We intend to disclose your data to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting Us using the contact details below or by amending your privacy settings by logging into your Account.

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a reasonable administrative fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information We hold about you.

Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that We do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

**8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes We may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and on our Website.

**9\. CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Cho-Yung (Cyprus) Ltd., Eressou 1, Mesa Geitonia, 4002, Limassol, Cyprus (VAT No: 10273919L), or [help@mycysupport.com](mailto:help@mycysupport.com)
